<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shut up Spotify!</title>
      <link>/posts/shutup_spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shutup_spotify/</guid>
      <description>Shut up Spotify!  ⊕ Myspace  (xkcd)    Apart from when I&amp;rsquo;m forced to work from home I have generally worked in open plan offices. One of my big fears each day is that I will open my laptop and whatever embarrassing song I was listening to will immediately start playing on full volume for everyone to hear.
Recently I bought a new pair of bluetooth headphones that conveniently allow you to connect to multiple devices at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How many gene annotations are there?</title>
      <link>/posts/how_many_annotations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how_many_annotations/</guid>
      <description>How many gene annotations are there? Grace Blackwell recently gave a really interesting talk on her work  Blackwell, G. A. et al. Exploring bacterial diversity via a curated and searchable snapshot of archived DNA sequences. Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory 2021.03.02.433662 (2021) doi:10.1101/2021.03.02.433662 generating a standardised and curated database of 661,405 bacterial genome assemblies using read data retrieved from the European Nucleotide Archive (ENA).
This dataset is already proving to be very useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Employment  Postdoctoral Research Fellow, University of Oslo Undergraduate Tutor, University of Cambridge Research Assistant, Walter and Eliza Hall Institute Optimisation Consultant, Biarri Commercial Mathematics Undergraduate Tutor, University of Melbourne  Education  PhD Mathematical Genomics, University of Cambridge &amp;amp; Wellcome Sanger Institute MSc Probability and Statistics, University of Melbourne BSc Applied Mathematics, University of Melbourne  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>This list is updated occasionally. A full list can be found on Google Scholar or Orcid.
† = joint authorship
Publications 2022 Mallawaarachchi, S., Tonkin-Hill, G., Croucher, NJ., Turner, P., Speed, D., &amp;amp; &amp;hellip; (2022). Genome-wide association, prediction and heritability in bacteria with application to Streptococcus pneumoniae. NAR Genomics and Bioinformatics. 4 (1), lqac011
Feng, Q., Tiedje, KE., Ruybal-Pesántez, S., Tonkin-Hill, G., Duffy, MF., Day, KP., &amp;amp; &amp;hellip; (2022). An accurate method for identifying recent recombinants from unaligned sequences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/</guid>
      <description>Up to date code and documentation for my software can be found on GitHub.
Software panaroo An error aware pipeline for pangenome investigation
fastbaps A fast approximation to a Dirichlet Process Mixture model (DPM) for clustering genetic data
pairsnp A set of scripts for very quickly obtaining pairwise SNP distance matrices from multiple sequence alignments using sparse matrix libraries to improve performance.
rhierbaps R package implementing the hierBAPS algorithm.
starmie R package developed with Stuart Lee to make post processing of population structure software output easier.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
