<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> PhD Candidate Mathematical Genomics, University of Cambridge &amp;amp; Wellcome Sanger Institute Research Assistant, Walter and Eliza Hall Institute MSc Probability and Statistics, University of Melbourne Optimisation Consultant, Biarri Commercial Mathematics BSc Applied Mathematics, University of Melbourne  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Chou, Evelyn S, Sabia Z Abidi, Marian Teye, Aleksandra Leliwa-Sytek, Thomas S Rask, Simon A Cobbold, Gerry Q Tonkin-Hill, et al. 2017. “A High Parasite Density Environment Induces Transcriptional Changes and Cell Death in Plasmodium Falciparum Blood Stages.” FEBS J., December. doi:10.1111/febs.14370.
 Lees, John A, Simon R Harris, Gerry Tonkin-Hill, Rebecca A Gladstone, Stephanie Lo, Jeffrey N Weiser, Jukka Corander, Stephen D Bentley, and Nicholas J Croucher. 2018. “Fast and Flexible Bacterial Genomic Epidemiology with PopPUNK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/</guid>
      <description>Starmie R package developed with Stuart Lee to make post processing of population structure software output easier.
 rhierBAPS R package implementing the hierBAPS algorithm.
 Plasmodium falciparum transcriptome analysis scripts Scripts used in analysing differential expression in Plasmodium falciparum transcriptome data.
 VAR gene assembly pipeline A pipeline for the assembly of Plasmodium falciparum VAR genes from short read RNA-seq data.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>