<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How many gene annotations are there?</title>
      <link>/posts/tufte-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tufte-features/</guid>
      <description>How many gene annotations are there? Grace Blackwell recently gave a really interesting talk on her work  Blackwell, G. A. et al. Exploring bacterial diversity via a curated and searchable snapshot of archived DNA sequences. Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory 2021.03.02.433662 (2021) doi:10.1101/2021.03.02.433662 generating a standardised and curated database of 661,405 bacterial genome assemblies using read data retrieved from the European Nucleotide Archive (ENA).
This dataset is already proving to be very useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Employment  Postdoctoral Research Fellow, University of Oslo Undergraduate Tutor, University of Cambridge Research Assistant, Walter and Eliza Hall Institute Optimisation Consultant, Biarri Commercial Mathematics Undergraduate Tutor, University of Melbourne  Education  PhD Mathematical Genomics, University of Cambridge &amp;amp; Wellcome Sanger Institute MSc Probability and Statistics, University of Melbourne BSc Applied Mathematics, University of Melbourne  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>This list is updated occasionally. A full list can be found on Google Scholar or Orcid.
* = joint authorship
Publications 2021 Gladstone, Rebecca A., Alan McNally, Anna K. Pöntinen, Gerry Tonkin-Hill, John A. Lees, Kusti Skytén, François Cléon, et al. 2021. “Emergence and Dissemination of Antimicrobial Resistance in Escherichia Coli Causing Bloodstream Infections in Norway in 2002–17: A Nationwide, Longitudinal, Microbial Population Genomic Study.” The Lancet Microbe, May. https://doi.org/10.1016/S2666-5247(21)00031-8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/</guid>
      <description>Up to date code and documentation for my software can be found on GitHub.
Software panaroo An error aware pipeline for pangenome investigation
fastbaps A fast approximation to a Dirichlet Process Mixture model (DPM) for clustering genetic data
pairsnp A set of scripts for very quickly obtaining pairwise SNP distance matrices from multiple sequence alignments using sparse matrix libraries to improve performance.
rhierbaps R package implementing the hierBAPS algorithm.
starmie R package developed with Stuart Lee to make post processing of population structure software output easier.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
