<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Gerry Tonkin-Hill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> PhD Candidate Mathematical Genomics, University of Cambridge &amp;amp; Wellcome Sanger Institute Research Assistant, Walter and Eliza Hall Institute MSc Probability and Statistics, University of Melbourne Optimisation Consultant, Biarri Commercial Mathematics BSc Applied Mathematics, University of Melbourne  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>† = joint authorship
Horesh, Gal, Grace A. Blackwell, Gerry Tonkin-Hill, Jukka Corander, Eva Heinz, and Nicholas R. Thomson. 2021. &amp;quot;A Comprehensive and High-Quality Collection of Escherichia Coli Genomes and Their Genes.&amp;quot; Microbial Genomics, January. https://doi.org/10.1099/mgen.0.000499.
Tonkin-Hill, Gerry†, Inigo Martincorena†, Roberto Amato, Andrew R. J. Lawson, Moritz Gerstung, Ian Johnston, David K. Jackson, et al. 2020. &amp;quot;Patterns of within-Host Genetic Diversity in SARS-CoV-2.&amp;quot; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory. bioRxiv. https://doi.org/10.1101/2020.12.23.424229.
Hamilton, William L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/</guid>
      <description>panaroo An error aware pipeline for pangenome investigation
 fastBAPS A fast approximation to a Dirichlet Process Mixture model (DPM) for clustering genetic data
 pairSNP A set of scripts for very quickly obtaining pairwise SNP distance matrices from multiple sequence alignments using sparse matrix libraries to improve performance.
 Starmie R package developed with Stuart Lee to make post processing of population structure software output easier.
 rhierBAPS R package implementing the hierBAPS algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>